http://vitalogicvitamins.com/privacy-policy

MenuReach For LifeDynamic HealthAll OneNatures LifeHFTSLife TimeVita LogicNatural BalanceThompsonNatural Sport
Sign Up  |  My Account  |  Log In  |  Log Out  |  View Cart  |  Email Us  |  Call 800-255-0867
Vitalogic Vitamins
Search:
Search
My Cart
Cart $0.00
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Product Support
If you have any questions regarding our products, or general inquiries, please feel free to send us a message and our excellent support team will reply back as soon as possible.
Home
/
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
When you register on our site, we collect your name, address, telephone number and email address, along with any other personal information that you voluntarily provide. When you place an order with us, we also collect your credit card number and card expiration date. We use this information to process and fill your order, to contact you about the order and in the case of voluntary information, to understand and serve you better. We will not provide for use or resell your information to any party outside of the company and its direct affiliates.
Please Recycle
About Vita Logic
About
Store Locator
Privacy Policy
Customer Service
Prop 65
Return Policy
Notice Regarding California Transparency in Supply Chains Act of 2010
These statements have not been evaluated by the FDA. These products are not intended to diagnose, treat, cure or prevent any disease.
© 2019 NutraMarks, Inc. All rights reserved.
The trademarks used herein are the registered trademarks of their respective owners.
These homeopathic products are based on traditional homeopathic practice and theory.
FDA has not evaluated these products and is not aware of scientific evidence to support homeopathy as effective.
60 day money back guarantee on homeopathic products! Free Guide to Homeopathics at
www.homeoguide.com.
To top
CCPA Notice     60 Day Satisfaction Guarantee     Privacy Policy
